<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

    <Beer.label>beer</Beer.label>
    <Beer.description>The first beverage besides water ever consumed by mankind. Beer can taste good, but its main effect is intoxication. Excessive consumption can lead to alcohol addiction.</Beer.description>

    <Wort.label>wort</Wort.label>
    <Wort.description>Beer before fermentation. The ingredients are mixed together, but this substance needs to ferment in a fermenting barrel before it becomes drinkable beer.</Wort.description>

    <Amphetamine.label>amphetamine</Amphetamine.label>
    <Amphetamine.description>An addictive stimulant. Amphetamine enhances cognitive performance, allowing users to work with great focus for extended periods of time, without getting tired. Addiction causes reduces mental performance and, sometimes, psychotic breaks with reality.</Amphetamine.description>

    <Joint.label>joint</Joint.label>
    <Joint.description>Marijuana leaves prepared and stuffed in small rolls of paper for smoking. The drug produces heightened mood and increased appetite, but reduces focus and ability to work. It also makes users hungry. Though not intensely addictive, cannabis use can produce a dependency.</Joint.description>

    <Crack.label>crack</Crack.label>
    <Crack.description>The free-base chemical form of the stimulant cocaine. Crack is the cheapest form of cocaine, but also the most addictive. Unlike other forms of cocaine, crack can be smoked, which speeds its uptake into the bloodstream. It induces an exceptionally rapid high in energy and mood. However, its effects are short-lived and the quick post-high depression makes it very addictive.</Crack.description>

    <Yayo.label>yayo</Yayo.label>
    <Yayo.description>The hydrochloride salt form of cocaine, yayo can be broken into a fine powder and snorted. The drug produces a euphoric high accompanied by a high in energy, reducing the user's need for rest. It also suppresses pain. Yayo can easily form an addiction.</Yayo.description>

    <GoJuice.label>go-juice</GoJuice.label>
    <GoJuice.description>A synthetic combat drug developed for space marines during the early days of interplanetary warfare. Go-juice blocks pain and brightens consciousness, increasing the user's focus, melee, and aiming abilities. It also strengthens large muscles, allowing users to move faster. However, chemists were never able to remove its addictive properties.</GoJuice.description>

    <MalariBlock.label>malari-block</MalariBlock.label>
    <MalariBlock.description>A drug for blocking malaria. Take every five days to keep malaria away.</MalariBlock.description>

</LanguageData>
